[{"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 8, "question": "You still take baths together in a huge bathtub with wine?", "qSentId": 7}, {"answer": "My sources.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 10, "question": "Well, what about that - where did you get that from?", "qSentId": 9}, {"answer": "I probably did.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 27, "question": "Did you wake up this morning and have a quick, you know?", "qSentId": 26}, {"answer": "Well, I'm a woman who's interested in a lot of things.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 47, "question": "What do you see your role as these days?", "qSentId": 46}, {"answer": "Yes, I like it.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 63, "question": "Any response?", "qSentId": 62}, {"answer": "Listening is one of them.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 85, "question": "But what do you think the secret of longevity in a marriage is?", "qSentId": 84}, {"answer": "My sources.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 93, "question": "Where'd you get that from?", "qSentId": 92}, {"answer": "Well, we've come pretty far.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 109, "question": "How far do you feel America has now come since then?", "qSentId": 108}, {"answer": "Yes, very much so.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 130, "question": "Are you pleased that President Obama got reelected?", "qSentId": 129}, {"answer": "I think he's a good man.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 132, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 131}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 140, "question": "Do you sleep well?", "qSentId": 139}, {"answer": "Probably not as well as you.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 143, "question": "How about you?", "qSentId": 142}, {"answer": "The bathtub is one of the ways.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 196, "question": "How are you doing this?", "qSentId": 195}, {"answer": "My hair back.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 207, "question": "What's that, honey?", "qSentId": 206}, {"answer": "Oh, she is great.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 247, "question": "It's great to be acting with those great actors, huh?", "qSentId": 246}, {"answer": "Oh, I love it.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 252, "question": "So you're enjoying the acting still?", "qSentId": 251}, {"answer": "You do.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 272, "question": "Are you kidding?", "qSentId": 271}, {"answer": "It's been a whirlwind, but I'm having so much fun.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 293, "question": "So this book you've written, \"Grace, God and Glory: My Leap of Faith\" - has an amazing set of pictures, by the way, how has your life been since this extraordinary summer you had in my home city?", "qSentId": 292}, {"answer": "I would say going to the White House and meeting the president.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 297, "question": "What's been the best moment?", "qSentId": 296}, {"answer": "Well, we had talked to him prior any of the Games, when we won team finals.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 299, "question": "What were his first words to you?", "qSentId": 298}, {"answer": "Yes, I mean he was telling me that he was so proud of me, and, you know, all hard work pays off.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 312, "question": "Did he say anything to you about -- about that part of this, that you also had achieved this extraordinary milestone?", "qSentId": 311}, {"answer": "Every day.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 315, "question": "How much do you have to work out a day?", "qSentId": 314}, {"answer": "Some days.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 320, "question": "I would imagine your routine is agonizing, right?", "qSentId": 319}, {"answer": "I used to be a top gymnast, actually.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 326, "question": "Are you -- are you sure?", "qSentId": 325}, {"answer": "No, I lied.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 328, "question": "Oh, really?", "qSentId": 327}, {"answer": "It takes a lot, not only the talent, but you have to be consistent and you have to dedicate your heart into the sport, and you have to work very hard and give 100 percent.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 343, "question": "-- what does it take to be a winner, winner, like a big winner?", "qSentId": 342}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 345, "question": "And you've got some boys in your life, Gabrielle?", "qSentId": 344}, {"answer": "I don't think that -- I don't -- no, no.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 357, "question": "I just want to go to a nightclub, meet a nice boy, give up gymnastics?", "qSentId": 356}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 359, "question": "So gymnastics is your real love, isn't it?", "qSentId": 358}, {"answer": "Yes, I mean just (INAUDIBLE).", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 377, "question": "Did you feel sad when you wrote it?", "qSentId": 376}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 383, "question": "Do you talk to him much?", "qSentId": 382}, {"answer": "It's pretty distant.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 386, "question": "Is it non-existent?", "qSentId": 385}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, I've been traveling everywhere.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 388, "question": "What do you -- why is this non-existent, do you think?", "qSentId": 387}, {"answer": "I -- I think he knows that.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 393, "question": "Do you think he knows that?", "qSentId": 392}, {"answer": "I love \"The Vampire Diaries.\"", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 425, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 424}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 428, "question": "As good as winning gold?", "qSentId": 427}, {"answer": "I'm five foot.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 443, "question": "How tall are you without those?", "qSentId": 442}, {"answer": "No, I am like very frugal, so I save my money.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 452, "question": "Are you spending all the money as fast as it's coming in?", "qSentId": 451}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 456, "question": "What's your big ambition now, Rio, presumably?", "qSentId": 455}, {"answer": "I hope so.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 458, "question": "Are you going to go there and kick butt and win more gold?", "qSentId": 457}, {"answer": "Well, my hero is definitely my mom.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 464, "question": "Who's your hero?", "qSentId": 463}, {"answer": "Dominique Dawes.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 467, "question": "And who's your sporting hero?", "qSentId": 466}, {"answer": "I really respect what he set for us.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 477, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 476}, {"answer": "Well, I don't think about that.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 511, "question": "How do you feel about that?", "qSentId": 510}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 517, "question": "You don't look in the mirror some mornings and think, I'm an icon?", "qSentId": 516}, {"answer": "There's the old saying of, of all the people who don't like me, just think of the millions who've never heard of me.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 526, "question": "Do you ever get anyone have a go at you?", "qSentId": 525}, {"answer": "Well, actually, it was a really easy book to write.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 532, "question": "When you finished the book, what did you think of your life?", "qSentId": 531}, {"answer": "Well, it's kind of -- you can't think about all of that at once.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 541, "question": "What do you -- what do you make of what's happened to you in those 80 years?", "qSentId": 540}, {"answer": "Oh, I'm very happy right now, yes.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 546, "question": "Are you a happy guy?", "qSentId": 545}, {"answer": "This -- yes, as happy as I ever hope to be right now.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 548, "question": "Is this the happiest you've ever been?", "qSentId": 547}, {"answer": "Yes, I did.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 556, "question": "Did you ever meet him?", "qSentId": 555}, {"answer": "We had a drink together, yes.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 559, "question": "You went drinking together?", "qSentId": 558}, {"answer": "I didn't check the label.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 561, "question": "ORGAN: (INAUDIBLE) Jack Daniels?", "qSentId": 560}, {"answer": "I probably did.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 576, "question": "But did you wake up this morning and have a quick, you know, a puff?", "qSentId": 575}, {"answer": "I think some people have more tolerance, you know, for smoking pot than others.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 582, "question": "Do you take a lot of it now?", "qSentId": 581}, {"answer": "Oh, I think it's progress, and I think it's, you know, a great step forward, and people are finally growing up and looking around the room and checking things out.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 597, "question": "Yes, what do you make of that?", "qSentId": 596}, {"answer": "(INAUDIBLE) very well.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 606, "question": "Why not?", "qSentId": 605}, {"answer": "That would be really hard to say, because, you know, this is -- I've just recorded a song with Dolly Parton that I think is the best song that I ever -- she wrote it and...", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 626, "question": "If you were consigned to a desert island and you could only listen to one song endlessly, on a permanent replay, what would you choose?", "qSentId": 625}, {"answer": "-- I told her, I think this is the best song I've heard in a long time.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 628, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 627}, {"answer": "Oh, I know it would work, because it would be better than the one we have, where there's still drugs available to anybody who wants them.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 639, "question": "-- that could be a strategy that works?", "qSentId": 638}, {"answer": "Well, as you probably know and have read, I'm completely against war.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 645, "question": "ORGAN: When you look at the wars in Iraq and Afghanistan, what do you think about America's position in the world, its foreign policy in particular in the last 12 years or so?", "qSentId": 644}, {"answer": "Well, if you believe in the Bible, which, of course, it says two things.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 654, "question": "Do you see any chance of actual peace in the Middle East?", "qSentId": 653}, {"answer": "Yes, I'm glad he got reelected.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 660, "question": "Were you -- were you pleased he got reelected?", "qSentId": 659}, {"answer": "Oh, I have voted, yes.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 676, "question": "You never voted for anybody?", "qSentId": 675}, {"answer": "No, I didn't.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 678, "question": "Did you -- did you this time?", "qSentId": 677}, {"answer": "Well, I had all kinds of excuses.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 680, "question": "Why not?", "qSentId": 679}, {"answer": "I really felt like Obama was going to win, that he did -- he didn't really need one more vote, that he had already had it sewn up.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 685, "question": "You didn't feel passionately enough about either candidate?", "qSentId": 684}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I've hunted all my life and (INAUDIBLE) when I was young, I had a bee-bee gun.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 688, "question": "What do you make of the gun debate in America?", "qSentId": 687}, {"answer": "Oh, very much, yes.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 721, "question": "Are you proud of them?", "qSentId": 720}, {"answer": "Well, yes.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 741, "question": "Do you think you've become a better husband?", "qSentId": 740}, {"answer": "Nothing.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 746, "question": "What have you learned about marriage?", "qSentId": 745}, {"answer": "Oh, yes.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 752, "question": "And yet, although you say that, you also always stayed fond of your exes, am I right?", "qSentId": 751}, {"answer": "Well, you said properly and...", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 760, "question": "So if I were to ask you how many, of all the girls you've loved before, we would reach, how many would it be?", "qSentId": 759}, {"answer": "ELSON: Well, that was not what I said.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 766, "question": "Well, how would you define properly?", "qSentId": 765}, {"answer": "Oh, I don't know.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 774, "question": "How many times have you been in love in your life?", "qSentId": 773}, {"answer": "Well, for the moment, she is.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 790, "question": "Is she the -- is she the real love of your life, would you say?", "qSentId": 789}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 802, "question": "ELSON: Do I ever sing songs to her?", "qSentId": 801}, {"answer": "Oh, 100 percent.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 806, "question": "You -- are you a romantic at heart?", "qSentId": 805}, {"answer": "I don't know, that's a -- that's a difficult one.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 815, "question": "If I could let you relive a moment, what would you choose?", "qSentId": 814}, {"answer": "Every time I go do a show where I show up and they show up and they come and clap and pay good money to hear, you know, hear me sing songs, it doesn't get any better than that.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 819, "question": "What's the great light (ph) for you, personally, for whatever reason?", "qSentId": 818}, {"answer": "Well, we are not substituting it, we still allow you to read the full story.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 862, "question": "How do the people that supply the original content feel about you nicking their stuff?", "qSentId": 861}, {"answer": "So we're kind of just taking it out (ph) by the user response.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 872, "question": "But where is the money?", "qSentId": 871}, {"answer": "I think the problem is with kind of the digital space is yes, the kind of publishers that have been around with print form for 50, 60, 70, 100 years, and now, I mean in the last five or six years, it's the mobile device has come into play.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 879, "question": "You think you guys just don't get it anymore, you should be doing XYZ?", "qSentId": 878}, {"answer": "I was thinking about this.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 889, "question": "What's your next great idea?", "qSentId": 888}, {"answer": "Yeah, very soon.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 895, "question": "You are going to be (INAUDIBLE)?", "qSentId": 894}, {"answer": "Well, that will be a great day, but I don't think -- look, to be honest, the thing at the moment I'm really focused on is just these users, you know, we have hundreds of thousands users rating it 5 stars in the app store.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 901, "question": "How are you going to deal with becoming stinking rich if that is what happens?", "qSentId": 900}, {"answer": "Yeah, I know.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 906, "question": "What about school, Nicholas?", "qSentId": 905}, {"answer": "I'm on a sabbatical leave at the moment.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 910, "question": "Are you at school?", "qSentId": 909}, {"answer": "Realistically I think I can find a way of doing both.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 915, "question": "Realistically?", "qSentId": 914}, {"answer": "Yeah, I do.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 917, "question": "You want to?", "qSentId": 916}, {"answer": "There is a lot of stuff beyond technology I want to do.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 921, "question": "Given that you created this world-beating app?", "qSentId": 920}, {"answer": "You know, Steve Jobs was actually the reason why I taught myself to program.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 924, "question": "Who are you heroes in the tech game?", "qSentId": 923}, {"answer": "Probably when I visited Yoko Ono in the Dakota building.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 929, "question": "What has been the single biggest pinch-me moment you've had so far?", "qSentId": 928}, {"answer": "'ALOISIO: Yeah.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 931, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 930}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "121222pmt", "aSentId": 935, "question": "She play \"Imagine\" for you while you were there?", "qSentId": 934}]